The only thing I've ever seen is something that you have to put in right before you eat it.
Just before you eat it, you have to put oil on it, like oil.
I can't get enough of that last part.
I couldn't get enough of it.
That's for sure.
It was the best!
It's true, you can eat ramen noodles during the day, but it's not so relaxing.
That's true, isn't it?
It's so-so, but it's good.
I'm glad it was so-so.
I'll never forget the taste at 10:00 p.m.
I couldn't forget it.
This is one big fork in the road for the future of dumpling bread, isn't it?
Learning Pot
Oh, no!
Here we are.
It sure would be nice to have an expedition, or something like that. It's nice. We'll eat at the hotel.
With the hotel's hot water.
It was very special.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was delicious.
Yes, yes. That's how it was,
Then, let me tell you something,
Let me tell you something.
Let's see...
Look, look, look.
I can really see it.
Should I tell them? I mean, the distribution people.
What?
If you can.
Yeah. - Yeah?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, but it's not easy.
Ever.
I'm working on it.
Right now.
I can't do it.
I was getting excited.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Hey.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well...
Well, let me out.
Yes, yes...
Let's see...
Well, then...
Yes, sir.
Well...
What should I do?
This...
I'll do it tomorrow.
So, if you have any more letters, please let me know.
I'd love to hear from any of you who have any suggestions for a good cup of ramen!
Wow, I'm curious.
I'd love to hear from you.
Thank you very much.
I'm out.
Hi. - Hi.
Good evening.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
Campeo, you're on fire.
Mariko was so excited. She made pigeons.
No, it was delicious.
Is this uniform? Yes, thank you.
Wow! What a great image quality!
It's so good, it's like seeing it with the naked eye.
It's like you're looking at it with the naked eye.
It was delicious. I'll never forget it.
I'll never forget it.
I can't forget it. -I know. -I'll never forget it.
That's bad, too. You just heat it up in a pot and it's ready to go.
They're selling them in vending machines these days.
They freeze all the noodles straight from the store.
So all you have to do is defrost them.
It's just like soup.
It tastes just like it did at the store.
Just the way it was. It was great.
It looks delicious.
But I think about it... I like cup ramen and standing-only noodle restaurants.
The more it becomes as good as a real soba restaurant, the more I feel disappointed.
I can't get enough of the instant feeling.
It's a little inferior.
It's okay. I don't have to be so sophisticated.
That's what I'm looking for.
You, who I liked, are not the kind of guy who does fashionable things like that.
Simple. That's nice.
That's what I'm looking for.
So ramen and cup ramen have certainly evolved, but basically, that guy's flavor was a little violent.
I couldn't get enough of it.
It's good.
I can't get enough of it.
Thank you very much.
I guess you are listening to the voice-only conversation as if it were on the radio.I know you all listen to voice-only conversations as if they were radio.
FM, Yokohama.
No, sir.
Somehow Point Seven.
FM.
Fujita.
Yes, yes, Fujita.
It's a familiar one.
It was delicious.
Yes, it was.
I just saw an ad for a woman with beautiful hair.
It's Pillai, isn't it?
That's for sure.
Thank you very much.
It's coming up.
Skip.
It is Kinichi, sir.
Yes.
I heard that a cup ramen called "Kaisen Gochujang Chige" is delicious.
Everyone seems to be on board.
Then, I would like to go to Kinichi block.
Yes, I'd like to go to the Kinichi block.
I heard that the instant noodles of the family lineage are also bad.
They are terrible.
They are good.
Probably because the technology to harden the noodles is much more advanced than in the past.
I see.
There you go.
Thanks for the food, Kinichi.
Almost fresh noodles.
Delicious.
Let's go to the real thing.
Here we go.
Fifty sheets.
Four, three.
Thank you!
Hello!
Please, please, please!
So, I don't know what's going on here, but..,
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know if I can tell you about the cup noodles.
Yes, you're right.
About cup ramen.
I'm sure you all love it.
Yes, I do.
By the way, that is really a wonderful Japanese culture,
I hear that foreigners are surprised when they come here.
Is that so?
Can foreigners eat it, Delicious!
I mean, I'm not sure if foreigners can eat it, Delicious!
Really.
Delicious.
Please give me your regards.
Please take care of it.
That's why,
Yes.
It's July 7th.
Here it comes! We've been waiting.
The Taramata Festival is not going to happen without waiting.
It's happening.
The people in town don't know.
Tara Tara.
The information.
This person doesn't know about it.
He just can't sing.
He's never performed in town.
It's not like that.
What kind of festival is it?
I've gone soft.
Yes, it was. It was tough.
But in a general sense, I can say,
The Milky Way is originally a big, big, big, big river.
It depends on the image.
The Orihime-like star, the Hikoboshi-like star, and the Milky Way,
The other one is a large triangle in summer,
The other one is the Great Triangle of Summer.
That's it.
Like the Petergius.
Like Petergius.
What do you think of this?
There's a big shiny one, isn't there?
Yes, there is.
That's why we call it the Great Triangle of Summer.
I really want to look at the night sky.
By the way, most of the time
It's often cloudy, isn't it?
No, that's right.
I've never seen it before.
It's a bad time.
That's right. I knew it.
Let's see..,
The Orihime star..,
In the constellation of the Phoenix.
The first-magnitude star, uh, Vega.
Vega.
He's a very strong guy in the Strike 2. Vega.
Is that so?
Like Ajah.
Like a boss character.A kind of boss character.
Vega.
Hikoboshi is a dual star.
Altair.
And,
First magnitude star in the constellation of the Phoenix,
Oh, wow. Deneb!
Deneb.
Hey, there's no Petergius or anything.
Petergius.
Altair, Vega.
Those three are the big triangle of summer.
Deneb.
Quickly, quickly.
This year, you can see it today, right? I hope so.
Do you want to see it? Do you want to see it? I want to see it.
I want to see it. Well, it doesn't really matter who's out on the street.
There was a starry-eyed guy who was really beautiful. Well, I've seen them, too.
Have you? Well, you know, even in Tokyo, it's a great location.
Yes, I've seen it. Well, it's hard to see the stars when the city is bright, isn't it?
That's right. I think so, in moderation.
That's right. It's quite dark in some places, so it's really beautiful.
I want to see it!
When city kids go to the countryside and say, "Wow, the stars are so beautiful," I say, "I live in the city.
Yeah, but it's totally possible.
Oh! Cool! It's a cool town! It's cute! Nice! Nice city!
It's awesome! A city where the stars are beautiful and look beautiful.
Yes, it is. It's a city! I love it.
It's really nice. And the hamburgers are delicious.
It's delicious and it's a nice town. It's a city not to be underestimated.
You can't be underestimated, Anadoret. It's a good town.
It's good because you're here, Anadole.
Yes, yes, yes. It's a good town.
It's a town. It's a good town.
So, let's go to this corner, shall we?
Yes, yes, yes.
Creatures of the Southern!
SOUTHERN!
So, we have another subject for you today.
Today's topic is in a foreign language, and if you listen to it in Japanese, you will understand it immediately.
Is that so?
In a foreign language.
I understand.
May I?
Yes.
Let's see...
What is it?
A little help.
Really?
I've never had anyone do it so nicely.
Are you sure?
May I?
Yes, ma'am.
The name of the living.
It's Spanish, by the way.
Spanish?
Yes, sir.
Mono
Mono.
mono
Like mono.
Huh?
Spanish.
But written in katakana, it's really mono
Ah, mono.
Mono.
Eh?
Don't cheat
Just in case
I'll show you something.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Mono.
Two letters.
Wow.
Mono.
Can anyone recognize it?
Yeah, I do.
Mono.
Oh, no.
Thank you.
Mono.
What? What?
All I got was an eraser.
Mono.
I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure.
All I see is erasers.
Yes.
Mono.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is it alive?
A living thing.
I don't know what that is.
Yes, sir.
It's a very major creature.
Major?
I know what it is.I definitely know what it is.
I'll let someone who doesn't know this creature tell you what it's good for.
What? Is that what this is?
Yeah, it's a thing.
A thing? A thing.
Moo... moo...
Just to spell it out, it's M-O-N-O, exactly.
Heh.
M O N O. Yes.
Let's write it down.
thing
Come on, yes, yes.
Really?
That's great, that's perfect.
This one?
I'm getting really confused.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What?
Huh?
Okay.
Well, I guess it's time for me to say goodbye.
Okay, bye.
I see you're still watching... and I'd like to see action 8, please.
I think you've got a good eye for rats.
Wow! That's what I'm talking about.
I wonder if it's a rat... that's a little bit crazy.
Oh, he's growing!
Spit out from here soon!
I used to pretend like this back in the Showa era.
Sensei, please...
Bang!
May I have a word? Are you a cow?
That's right.
Mescal!
Wow. It's amazing to see it from overhead.
That's amazing.
If you look at it like a monitor, it's amazing.
You probably tried to paint this black, right?
Oh, yes, that's right.
Is this a little too much in some places?
This is a mystery.
Normally, you would paint it black, right? Why is it like this?
Why is it like this?
I opened it.
About 10 billion.
We have more time.
I see.
It's all black. And inside there, too.
So, now that I look at this, I see that everyone knew about it.
What! That's great!
Really?
That's great.
Wow.
Didn't you check it out?
Well, well, well, well.
By the way, "thing" is Spanish for this.
Sal?
Hey.
So hairy.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
What?
It's an aggregate.
Where's the aggregation?
There's only one.
I'm so sorry.
There's another one.
I'm sorry. My hair.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I did get in there because there was a lot of hair.
Hairy? What do you mean hairy?
You mean hairy?
When I said hairy, I probably meant one of them.
What? I'm sorry.
I'm surprised. I didn't realize it could be one of them.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's really bad.Oh, I'm sorry for a minute. It's really bad.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, is your hair okay? My place.
It's different.
It's something about the thickness, the shortness, the way it all comes together.
It was an apple.
I see.
It was an apple, wasn't it?
I don't know.
Well, well, well.
So you're a monkey.
A monkey.
Monkey.
Well, in English, it's monkey.
Oh, I see.
There are still some vestiges of it.
Yes, it does.
Monkey.
Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
Well, well, well, well.
Interesting.
Well, let's see.
Well, uh, I'd like to, uh, have a little more, uh, correspondence with you guys.
Communication.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
How about it?
Oh, I have something for you.
There it is!
That's it, isn't it?
Do you have something for me?
What's that? What's with the dumpling buns?
What's the matter? What's going on all of a sudden?
What's with the dumpling buns?
What's the matter?
What day were you born?
I was born on June 12.
Ehhhh...
That means, in terms of time, you just celebrated your birthday, didn't you?
That's right.
Yes, I did.
22, 22, 20?
Twenty-three.
Three years old.
Is he/she 3 years old now?
Yes, I am.
So please wait a moment.
What?
No way.
No way?
Ta-da!
Yes!
Yeah! What is it?
What is it? What is this?
What is this?
Founded in... Kyoto?
Looks amazing!
It looks amazing!
It's like this.
There's something amazing in here.
What is it? Can I open this?
Go ahead.
Oh, my God! This is... wow!
It's wrapped in... nice paper. It's wrapped in nice paper.
I want to blot it.
What is it? Shall we open it?
Manjuu.
What is it?
Manjuu for my birthday! It's a manju with manju claws.
Manjuu? Manjuu...
What's that called?
What does it mean?
It's like the shape of a jar.
That's right.
It's some kind of ball...
What is it?
It says "Kundama-do".
Kundamado?
But it smells so good.
What is it?
Scent.
Could it be...
Excuse me.
Open.
What?
What is it? What is it?
It's written in English?
Yes, it is.
Oh, I see. So foreigners buy it because it's from Kyoto.
Oh, I see.
What is it?
Oh, look out!
Oh, what is this?
What is this?
Whoa!Wow!
Beautiful!
Hey, is that...
Somebody... somebody.
I'm sorry. You're right.
Why, I didn't want to cause a reaction.
I was just, uh, trying to keep it out of focus.
Oh, I see.
So, so, so...
It smells good.
What is it?
Candles!
I'll open all the candles.
Candles.
We got candles.
It's the season in another way. Candles.
Oh, how stylish!
These are candles.
It's wrapped right now.
Because it's in season.
Seasonal!
It smells so good!
What's that smell?
It's kind of amazing!
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow!
It smells so good!
Oh, my God.
Oh, this?
Here.
Oh, so when you light it, it smells like... what?
What? Why is there a comb on it?
There's a fire in it, too.
What does that mean?
How does it work?
What is it? This...
It's an elephant hair comb.
What?
Elephant hair comb.
Elephant hair? Elephant hair comb?
Elephant tusk?
What?
Oh, my God!
Thank you!
I'm a little confused.
What's this on? This...
Candles.
Aromatic.
What is this?
This aroma is on the stone.
I want to open this one. What is this? It's got a manual in it.
It's electric. What's that? It's just a little aromatic oil that you put on the stone.
You put your favorite aroma oil on it and then you enjoy it. It's like an aroma stone.
It smells so good. The candles are so nice.
I'll do it.
Oh, my God, I can't believe it's wrapped in another candle!
Thank you.
Thank you, everybody, 23 years old.
Oh, that's the one you can open.
It's wrapped up nice and tight.
How many of these do we have before we hit it?
There were several, but this is the last one.
All of these... just keep turning them over and turning them over.
And then you can start flipping through the channels like this.
It smells so good. It smells so good.
It smells so good.
Thank you very much. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. I'm gonna brush my hair with this.
What's with the hair?
Hair is a woman's life.
She's from the Showa period. She was saying that.
Like my grandma used to say.
Protect your hair no matter what.
Thank you very much.
I'll use it.
Pumice stone.
I'll have to buy some aromatherapy oil.
I see. I see. The oil is another thing.
Oil's another thing. You can smell it any way you like.
Thank you. I'm glad.
Who selected these?
P himself.
Thank you. You know what you're doing.
Mr. Kikan, this is P. Basically, he has money.
Yes, you should include the manual.
I'm glad. This makes me happy.
I knew it! I knew it!
I knew it. I thought so too.
I thought so too. Why bother putting out candles now?
Candles for sure!
Don't get involved.
You're right. Don't get involved.
They're charging up to a whole new level!
Congratulations! The live performance at the center was great!
Thank you very much. Happy 23rd Chai.
Happy birthday again!Dumpling buns, happy birthday once again.
Thank you very much
They're here.
Short hair for a cute dumpling bun.
I'm so happy! What a waste of this!
This wrapping paper is cool, too.
It's really cool.
It looks like a tote.
It's so stylish!
It's a cream color... a light cream color.
This brown.
Her hair is really nice.
It's very nice. It's like a bridge.
Yes, it's bridge-like.
It's not normal hair.
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
It's a perm.
That's why.
Well, then...
Well...
Well, for now...
Is this okay here?
Yes, sir.
This week.
I mean...
I see... time-wise, it's not Tanabata yet.
That's right.
What month is it?
It's still June.
As of today, it's June.
June 11th.
The rainy season hasn't ended yet.
There was no rainy season at all.
But it hasn't rained much, has it?
But maybe...
The front is coming.
Yes, it's coming.
And it's going to rain a little bit.
Yes, sir.
Well, here we go.
And the starter...
They're here.
What's next week?
Evism.
I'm going to the Osaka show.
He's coming.
I'm so happy. Thank you all.
I'm so glad.
Twenty-three.
It wasn't 32.
I'd hate it if it was the other way around.
I'm not done yet.
By the way...
Next week in blue.
Next week, not just a little bit.
That's right.
The show reopens on July 19th.
That's a long way off.
That's a long time.
I'm still trying to figure out why it's open.
High school baseball games?
But there was a qualifying round last year, too.
Baseball qualifiers.
Oh, City College Baseball.
There's no such thing as husband-wife communication, is there?
Really?
Uh huh...
Uh...
Why do you think I'd like to see you there again?
I think you'll forget.
I won't forget.
You'll forget?
I can't forget.
No, no, no, no.
I'll do something about the show.
Oh, my God, don't forget.
Please don't forget me.
Yeah, really.
I'm writing to Tanahata.
I'll make it simple.
Don't forget.
Don't forget... your debut in the museum.
I'll eat.
Well, there are plenty of other shows that could take your place.
That's not true.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
We shouldn't say that.
There are many good shows in this time slot.
But, you know...
We're good, too.
Of course.
It's a good show.
Well, I'll see you on July 19th.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations. Thank you.Congratulations. Thank you.